atptour.com 2016-06-16

# Privacy Policy | ATP World Tour | Tennis

ATP Tour, Inc. ("ATP") is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read this Privacy Policy, as well as our [Terms of Use Agreement] for more details about how we use information you submit to the Website. This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Use Agreement, constitute the entire agreement between you and ATP. By your use of the Website you consent to be governed by this Privacy Policy.

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 (THIRTEEN) YEARS OLD, PLEASE TALK TO YOUR PARENTS BEFORE USING THE WEB SITE OR PROVIDING YOUR NAME OR OTHER INFORMATION TO THE WEB SITE. YOU CANNOT SUBMIT INFORMATION TO THE WEB SITE WITHOUT YOUR PARENT'S PERMISSION.

1\. PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

You can visit the Web site without disclosing any information about yourself. However, to participate in any interactive features including, but no limited to contests, forums, games, download any Content, receive information from ATP such as mobile alerts, newsletters or email regarding news, results, ATP products, tickets alerts, and partners offers, (collectively, the "Services") you must register and provide accurate information about yourself to the Web site, as the Services may not work properly without such information.

Additionally, the Web site contains links to web sites that are not operated by ATP, such as the companies which operate Fantasy Tennis and the ATP Shop. These third parties may collect data from you and share some of that data with us. ATP is careful when choosing its partners, sponsors, and affiliates, but ATP is not responsible for any misuse of personal information by such third parties. We recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each web site that you use to confirm that the site's policies are acceptable to you.

When using the Services, we may ask you to provide all or some of the following information: your name, your address (including city, state/province, country and zip/postal code, your email address, your telephone numbers, your date of birth, your gender ("Personal Information"). We may also ask you to provide your thoughts or answer some questions about your favorite ATP events, personalities, and other subjects of interest to tennis fans. Your Personal Information is password protected, and any Personal Information you provide to the Web site is protected from unauthorized disclosure by reasonable technological measures. Information provided to ATP is not, however, transmitted via SSL encryption technology. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. At no time will an employee of ATP ask for your password via email. If you have any questions about your Personal Information, please contact Jeffrey T. Reel, Vice President and General Counsel, ATP - Legal Dept., 201 ATP Boulevard Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida 32082. With your consent, Personal Information may be used for marketing and promotional communications by ATP, its partners, sponsors, affiliates, successors, and assigns. ATP will, not, however, sell or lease your personal information to third-parties not associated with ATP, its partners, sponsors, and affiliates. ATP believes that tennis fans will appreciate receiving information regarding ATP events and players. However, ATP respects the right of each fan to decide whether to receive such information. If you do not wish to receive marketing and promotional communications from us or our partners, sponsors, and affiliates, you can choose to customize your product email opt-ins by logging in to your account and simply opting out to the specific product. If you would like to close your account with us and delete your profile, please login to the Fan Credential preference center and click on ‘Remove My Account’. You can also unsubscribe to our mailings lists from the link found in each mailings.

The Web site or ATP may be sold, or other transactions may occur in which your Personal Information is one of the business assets transferred by ATP. In such a case, your Personal Information may be one of the business assets we transfer, and you hereby agree to such transfer.

2\. AGGREGATED INFORMATION

To evaluate the web site and ensure that we are providing Content and Services of interest to you, we may collect and store statistical information regarding how you use the Web site, the name of your Internet Service Provider, the Web site that referred you to the Web site, and the time and date you view the Web site. We may also use Personal Information to develop demographic information regarding Web site users by implementing Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Such aggregated information will not identify you personally. We may share this aggregated, statistical information with our partners, sponsors, affiliates, and other third-parties. If you wish to opt out of Google Analytics tracking, please click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) and download and install the add-on for your web browser.

3\. COOKIES

From time to time ATP may place a cookie on your computer. A "cookie" is a small line of code that is stored in your browser when you visit a cookie-enabled Web site. A cookie allows us to track and keep records on user activity. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, it is possible that some parts of the Web site will not function. Moreover, in order to use the Services, your browser must accept cookies.

4\. DISCLOSURE FOR LAW ENFORCEMENT PURPOSES

ATP reserves the right to access and disclose Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly, or to protect itself or others. ATP may attempt to obtain the prior consent of the individual before disclosing the Personal Information, but it has no obligation to do so.

5\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

ATP reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Please review this Policy from time to time to ensure your familiarity with its terms. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Jeffrey T. Reel, Vice President and Assistant General Counsel, ATP - Legal Dept., 201 ATP Boulevard, Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida 32082.

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

The safety of children, both online and off line, is important to ATP and all of its members. So, if you are under the age of 13, please ask your parents to look at this page with you before you submit any information to the ATP Web site.

PARENTS & GUARDIANS:

This Web site is a general audience Web site. We do not knowingly collect and/or share Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen on the Web site. However, your child cannot use some of the interactive features or Services of the Web site, such as the Contest or Message Features, without providing Personal Information. We therefore recommend using the Web site with your child if he or she is interested in participating in an interactive feature of the site. If, in the future, ATP collects Personal Information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.

©2015 ATP Tour, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
